现在让我们看看我们所说的边缘问题。如果我尝试计算像素值
Let’s look now at what we call the edge problem. If I try and compute the pixel value
在该特定坐标处，输入图像中的像素窗口必须看起来像
at this particular coordinate the window of pixels in the input image has to look like
这个。而问题在于，一些输入窗口已经脱离了边缘
this. And the problem is that some of the input window has fallen off the edge of the
图片。因此，有些像素值未定义：窗口需要像素值
image. So there are pixel values that are undefined: the window requires pixel values
在输入图像中不存在。这有几个解决方案：一个解决方案
that do not exist in the input image. There’s a couple of solutions to this: one solution
当窗口从边缘掉落时，我们只是不计算输出值。那
is we simply don’t compute the output value whenever the window falls off the edge. That
将是所有指示的像素，在右侧图像中进行散列。我们刚刚
would be all the pixels that are indicated, hashed out in the right-hand image. We just
无法计算那些。另一种选择是假设图像
wouldn’t be able to compute those. Another option is to assume that the image
由全部设置为零的像素包围。如果我们放一层零像素全部
is surrounded by pixels that are all set to zero. If we put a layer of zero pixels all
然后我们可以在图像边缘确定一个有效的窗口并从有效窗口中确定
around the edge of the image then we can determine a valid window and from the valid window we
可以计算我们的功能。问题是零点有点人为而且它们
can compute our function. The problem is that the zeros are somewhat artificial and they
当然会影响函数返回的结果。另一种技术是复制
will, of course, influence the result returned by the function. Another technique is to replicate
边缘像素。在边缘周围复制这些像素;将它们堆叠在图像周围
the edge pixels. Make copies of those pixels around the edge; stack them around the image
这样我们总是有有效的像素值进入窗口。
so that we always have valid pixel values going into the window.
所有这些选择都有不同的优点和缺点;只是要意识到这个问题
All of these options have different advantages and disadvantages; just be aware of the problem
当您在图像上执行空间操作时，在某些环境中可能会执行空间操作
when you are performing spatial operations on images and in some environments there may
是您可以传递给软件的选项，告诉它如何处理这种边界条件。
be options you can pass into the software to tell it how to handle this boundary condition.
我们可以看到窗口从输入图像边缘掉落的效果为暗
We can see the effect of the window falling off the edge of the input image as a dark
我们的输出图像边缘周围的边框。我们来看看我们计算出的这个图像
border around the edge of our output image. Let’s have a look at this image we computed
不久之前。如果我们在这里放大边缘，我们可以看到相当快速的下降
a short time ago. If we zoom in on the edge here, we can see quite a rapid drop off in
当我们接近图像的边缘时灰度级，这是由于邻域
grey level as we approach the edge of the image, and this is due to the neighbourhood
窗口从输入图像的边缘掉下来。另一件需要注意的是窗口
window falling off the edge of the input image. Another thing to be aware of is that the window
大小总是奇数-它是一个方形窗口，宽度和高度总是奇数
size is always odd—it is a square window and the width and the height are always odd
数字。原因如下：窗口是方形的，它始终居中
numbers. The reason for this is the following: the window is square and it is always centred
在输入像素上。假设边缘大多数像素距离中心H像素。
on the input pixel. Let’s say that the edge most pixel is H pixels away from the centre.
在这种特殊情况下，H将等于2.从中间像素移动，我们步进
In this particular case, H would be equal to 2. Move from the middle pixel, we step
右边两个像素，我们位于窗口边缘的像素处。以便
two pixels to the right and we are at a pixel which is on the edge of the window. So that
然后，窗口宽度是2H+1.H是整数;2H+1总是奇数。
means, then, that the window width is 2H + 1. H is an integer; 2H + 1 is always an odd number.